{
    "id": "66a0f363ec694fb7be3e0ca125c54e38",
    "title": "Because And Because Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We cancelled the trip ………………….. the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I helped him ………………… I liked him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was all ……………….. my mother that I reached where I am today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to hurry up ………………… you are already late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late …………………. my car broke down on the way home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard ……………….. she wanted to pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I sat down to rest ………………… I was tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t get the job ………………. she didn’t apply in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. his strange accent, people assume that he is a foreigner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his job ………………… his drug problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}